Guide to the Vanguard Press Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Photographs
  - Kamm, Josephine (Box 196)
  - Kasdan, Sara (Box 196)
  - Labin, Suzanne (Box 196)
  - Langner, Nola (Box 196)
  - Leighton, Frances S. (Box 196)
  - Lewis, Arthur H. (Box 196)
  - Lieber, Leslie & Miller, Toni (Box 196)
  - Loveland, Constance (Box 196)
  - McKown, Robin (Box 196)
  - Marcotte, Gilles (Box 196)
  - Markora, Alicia (Box 196)
  - Michaels, Leonard SEE: Various (Box 196)
  - Montgomery, Charlotte (Box 196)
  - Murphy, James M. (Box 196)
  - Noel-Baker, Francis (Box 196)
  - Perry, Ralph B. (Box 196)
  - Philipson, Morris (Box 196)
  - Pidoll, Carl (Box 196)
  - Price, Stanley (Box 196)
  - Rahe, Peter (Box 196)
  - Read, Grantly D. (Box 196)
  - Ross, George (Box 196)
  - Roth, Holly (Box 196)
  - Ruhm, Herbert (Box 196)
  - Sager, Gordon (Box 196)
  - St. Marcoux (Box 196)
  - Shamir, Moshe (Box 196)
  - Shannon, William (Box 197)
  - Shippey, Lee (Box 197)
  - Slade, Caroline (Box 197)
  - Slobodkin, Louis (Box 197)
  - Smith, Pauline (Box 197)
  - Spinelli, Marcos (Box 197)
  - Stafford, Jean SEE: Various (Box 197)
  - Tanner, Patrick (Box 197)
  - Thompson, Francis (Box 197)
  - Toscanini, Auturo (Box 366)
  - Vanguard (Box 197)
  - Various: Jean Stafford; Kurt Vonnegut, Jr.; Leonard Gardner; Leonard Michaels; Joyce Carol Oates (Box 197)
  - Venezis, Ilias (Box 197)
  - Vlachos, Ange (Box 197)
  - Vonnegut, Kurt SEE: Various (Box 197)
  - Willingham, Calder Oversize in Box 198 (Box 197)
  - Winsten, Stephen (Box 197)
  - Wolfson, P.J. (Box 197)
  - Wood, Charles Erskine Scott (Box 197)
  - Duplicate photographs from the collection (Box 197A)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Box 198)
  - Willingham, Calder (Box 198)
- Series VIII: Clippings
  - Bellow, Saul - Boulle, Pierre (Bridge) (Box 199)
  - Boulle, Pierre (Desperate - Face) (Box 200)
  - Boulle, Pierre (Garden - My) (Box 201)
  - Boulle, Pierre (My -Noble) (Box 202)
  - Boulle, Pierre (Not - Photograpger) (Box 203)
  - Boulle, Pierre (Planet - Time) (Box 204)
  - Dennis, Patrick - Doctor Seuss (500 - Mulberry) (Box 205)
  - Farrell, James T. (All - Duplicates) (Box 206)
  - Farrell, James T. (Duplicates - Studs) (Box 207)
  - Farrell (Studs) - Naipaul, V.S. (Mystic) (Box 208)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Assassins - Childwold) (Box 209)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Crossing - Do) (Box 210)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Do - Expensive) (Box 211)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Expensive - Garden) (Box 212)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Garden - Goddess) (Box 213)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Goddess - New) (Box 214)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Night - Poisoned) (Box 215)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Reviews - Them) (Box 216)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Them) (Box 217)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Them) (Box 218)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Unholy - Upon) (Box 219)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Wheel - With) (Box 220)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Wonderland) (Box 221)
  - Sitwell, Edith (Book - Collected) (Box 222)
  - Sitwell, Edith (English - Eccentrics) (Box 223)
  - Sitwell (Gardeners) - Willingham, Calder (Eternal) (Box 224)
  - Willingham (Geraldine - Secret) (Box 225)
  - Willingham (Providence) - Wraight, A.D. (Box 226)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol Printed Material (Box 227)